The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Thirty-Sixth Episode
The Spell of Mephisto
Is the roast lizard ready?
Bring the bat eye soup immediately!
What's wrong, Hecate?
Aren't you eating anymore?
- No, I'm full now.
- Eat!
You'll never become a
great witch if you eat so little!
- Hurry up!
- Yes, sir!
Here we are with the dishes,
with the delicacies we've cooked!
Such treats!
I had today's menu prepared...
..taking into account the
diet you have to follow.
- Here you go!
- Here you go! - Here you go!
Eat, Hecate! The lizard
will make you tenacious..
and the bat eye soup
will make you cunning!
Come on, eat, Hecate!
The fire has gone out!
What happened? What is it?
What's going on?
It's Mother!
Mother is back!
Your mother is back, you say?!
Damn,
the peace and quiet is over!
It's nice to return
after a long absence.
I hope Hecate has become
a great witch.
Let's go home!
I'm here, my dears!
Welcome back!
- Dearest!
- Hecate, how are you?
I was so worried
thinking about you,
that I couldn't
think of anything else!
Not even during the conference!
That damned witches'
conference never ended!
It lasted
a whole long year!
Have you made progress
in your witchcraft lessons?
Have you agreed to receive the heart
of Princess Sapphire,
which your father
told me about in the letter?
Her girl's heart!
You will be a perfect witch
with the heart of a Princess!
Now show me
what you have learned!
- Come on! Go ahead!
- Dear... Dear...
Well, you know... I don't know if...
What the hell are you muttering?
Speak more clearly!
Hecate hasn't yet...
hasn't learned yet!
What? Not yet?! It's not possible!
Hecate, say: have you not yet
become a witch? Is it true?!
And I who had placed
so many hopes in you!
- Forgive me, mother...
- Forgive you?!
Darling, I still haven't
managed to get Sapphire's heart!
I'd take a hammer to that
eggplant head of yours...
until it becomes a real pumpkin!
I'd like to know what the
hell you've been doing all year!
I spread the word
to the four winds...
...saying that I have a daughter
who is a real witch and you...
How does this make
me look now?! Damn it!
Fine then!
I'll take care of it myself!
But I'll do it my way, not like that
incompetent father of yours did.
Very soon I will make of you
a true witch!
That girl named Sapphire,
or whatever else she is called,
- does she still live in the castle?
- Yes, of course!
- Let me help you, dear!
- No! You stay and take care of the house!
What a beautiful day!
A "forget-me-not"!
I wonder what the language
of "forget-me-nots" is..!
Let's see..
Is it a secret?
It's true, it's a secret!
That day,
Prince Franz told me:
"I like you, beautiful girl,
and I like how you dance very much!"
Secret! Secret!
Teddy bear, do you know the language
of "forget-me-nots"?
I have a pleasant secret
unknown to everyone,
but I think that to you
I will end up telling it.
Princess!
Who are you to penetrate into the
most secret part of the castle?
Smell that fragrance!
Anyone who smells the scent
of my flowers becomes a doll,
a charming doll
and obedient to its master!
Stand up, doll!
Go to Mephisto's cave! Go!
Go to Mephisto's cave!
And go there alone!
It would be easy for me to take you there
but I, Lady Hell,
admired by all the witches,
won't do it.
Go on your own!
This is my way
of doing things.
Listen, Hecate,
for your father's sake...
Don't keep repeating
that you don't want to become a witch,
otherwise your mother
will fly into a rage!
Won’t you tell me why you don't
study witchcraft like the other witches?
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
No! No! I don't want to become
a witch!
Soon they will bring
Sapphire here and then I...
No! No! I must find
a way to stop it!
Maybe...
Maybe I have an idea to help her!
Let's go to Mephisto's mountain,
Opal.
Oh, Sapphire!
Mephisto's mountain,
Mephisto's mountain...
Sapphire, don't go!
But I must go.
What’s the matter, Sapphire?
Mom made you smell the drug
that turns people into dolls!
Poor Sapphire...!
I wonder if Mom
put the drug here!
Is it an important flower?
- Franz...
- Franz?
He is the Prince of Goldland.
His name is Franz.
My Franz
is the most beautiful Prince there is.
It seems to me that you like him a lot, right?
Then I'll take you to his palace!
Follow me, horse!
Let's go to Goldland!
I am certain that Prince Franz
will help her!
Sapphire is not here!
And neither is Hecate!
May I know
what the hell you have done?
Don't be angry, dear!
We can easily find out
where Sapphire is with the magic ball.
Magic ball, tell me!
Oh, Sapphire! But she is not headed here!
Oh, heavens! Perhaps my spell
has broken!
No, it's impossible!
Get ready to go out, quickly!
Go out?! But where do you want to go?
To Goldland, blockhead!
What good is that ball to you,
if you don't even know how to see
where everyone is headed?!
Hey, look at that strange cat!
It looks like he has it in for us!
He's dancing really well..
I think he escaped from a circus
Sleep!
Here we are, Sapphire!
This is the Prince's chamber.
Wait a moment!
He will see us soon.
Please, come in!
Who is it? What do you want?
Princess Sapphire!
I am happy to see you, Sapphire!
How kind this Prince is!
How are you? Why aren't you speaking?
What is wrong?
Sapphire, you are acting strange!
Do you feel unwell?
He has a pleasant appearance
that inspires confidence.
Prince Frank, a stranger
has forced his way into the castle!
A stranger?!
Sapphire, perhaps you
I think I understand..
There is no stranger
in here!
Open the door
and let me make sure!
Someone forced their way
into the castle?!
Oh, Your Highness!
I'll inspect the room
myself! Get out of the way!
Yes, sir!
Franz! It's me: your uncle
Chanel! Open the door!
Yes, uncle, just a moment!
Come here, I have an idea!
Please, come in, Uncle Chanel.
If you find anyone, you
can arrest them if you like.
Franz, who is this lady?
Lady? But look at her
closely, Uncle Chanel!
It's a doll that a dear
friend of mine gave me.
I had to put it on the
sofa because it's too big...
...to be able to fit it in a drawer.
She really looks like a girl
A girl with beautiful long hair!
Damn, she looks like the one from the dream!
Franz? Franz! Franz!
You are contemplating that doll
as if you wanted to marry her!
- Marry her?!
- Now listen to me carefully, Franz!
What do you think of this lady?
Maybe she isn't very beautiful, it's true,
but she is very rich.
- I don't want her!
- Please, be reasonable!
At least get engaged to her!
She will bring us a dowry
of a billion Yen.
With that sum, Goldland
will be able to do great things!
I said no!
I don't like marrying
for interest, Uncle!
- I will choose the one who will be
my wife. - You selfish fool!
Do what I tell you, or else
marry this damned doll!
Of course I would! And right now!
Don't make fun of your uncle!
This time I will succeed
in making you marry her!
If you don't say yes to her by Christmas,
I will kick you out of the castle!
I will never obey him, Sapphire
I won't let you escape this time.
I would even be capable of giving my life for you.
Sapphire, what happened to you? It's as if you were truly a doll.
Did you listen to the conversation?
Let's break through the roof and take her away!
Break through the roof?! How foolish you are!
Any poor devil would do that!
What's wrong?
I'm not surprised at all that you haven't been able, in so many years,
to make Hecate a real witch!
But I am not like you!
- How do I look?
- Wonderful, dear!
You are beautiful! But may
I ask what you intend to do?
Wait and you will see how
I will manage to succeed.
I am very happy to meet
you. Who are you, Princess?
I am Princess De Streghis
and I come from Hell.
And I am her faithful servant:
Stotten!
And what have you come to do
in Goldland?
I, really.
Tell him, Stotten!
The Princess fell in love at
first sight with Prince Franz,
during the last military parade.
Really?
We would be delighted if you would accept
our introductory gift.
Please forgive us
if it is perhaps a bit too small.
Do not be surprised!
We use diamonds...
...instead of gravel,
in our country!
Diamonds instead of gravel?!
Poor fool!
They are just pebbles!
Therefore we will give you
as many as you want!
If Princess De Streghis and
Prince Franz become engaged,
we will also give you a thousand tons
of ancient coins.
A thousand tons?!
A thousand tons...
A thousand tons of ancient coins!
King Chanel, what do you say to this
marriage proposal of ours?
A thousand tons of ancient coins!
Chanel, then, do you agree?
Of course I agree!
It will be the most beautiful
engagement in the world!
Prince Franz will
also agree.
- Stotten!
- Congratulations, Princess!
Let's get down to business! You must offer her
a token of engagement.
Certainly, with pleasure!
I'll order the ring right away!
I would like something
different from a ring.
Anything you wish!
I've heard that Prince
Franz has a beautiful doll.
What? You would like his doll?!
Is it strange, perhaps,
to ask for a doll?
Absolutely! There is
nothing strange about it!
I'll bring it to you right away! Wait for
me here a second! I'm going to get it!
It seems your plan
worked, dear.
Open up! Open up! Franz,
open the door right now!
Franz, give me the doll!
I won't give it to you for any reason!
It isn't very high.
Curtains, twist yourselves!
Form a rope!
Why are you pulling me?
Damn it, break down the door!
Franz! Franz, where are you?
The window!
He's in the courtyard!
Inspect the courtyard!
Hurry, Sapphire! Hurry!
Hurry! We will hide there!
Poor me, this is a chapel!
I can't go in there,
because I am the daughter of Mephisto.
Sapphire, do not fear!
I will never leave you.
I will fight against anyone
who wants to hurt you,
- even if it were my uncle!
- Did you find him?
- No!
- Look again!
Quick!
Princess De Streghis,
I will have the doll before evening!
She's gone! The jewels..!
What the hell happened?
It didn't go well.
Shut up, you idiot! I left
because I have another plan in mind.
This drug turns
all creatures into stone.
Look!
Ah, it really works!
And all those
who drink this water..
.will be turned into stone!
I don't understand: Princess
De Streghis disappears,
the jewels become stones..
Have you not found Franz yet?
What are you waiting for?!
Go and find him immediately!
Stone! Stone!
My soldiers have
all turned into stone!
This must be the work of Mephisto!
Mephisto! Mephisto!
Is there no one here?
Is there no one left
in this castle?
They've all
turned to stone!
Oh, look! There's King Chanel!
It's Mephisto! Mephisto is
definitely in this castle!
Sapphire, something is
wrong. I'm going to check.
Prince Frank, no!
You mustn't go out!
Oh, he's already gone!
It's too quiet.
But that's my uncle!
He isn't moving at all!
Let's go have a look...
But he's turned to stone! This
is certainly the work of Mephisto!
- Mephisto!
- Boy, bring Sapphire here!
- I won't do it!
- Bring Sapphire here,
Otherwise I will hurt you.
I will defend her at the cost of my life!
On your guard!
Hail Mephisto!
To me, wind!
And now bring out Sapphire!
Come and get her, if you are capable!
- Close that door!
- I'll take care of it!
Stone lion,
flood the Chapel!
The water!
- The water!
- Sapphire, you've regained consciousness!
- Yes, Franz.
- Oh, Sapphire...
Franz! Franz!
- Franz!
- Sapphire! Sapphire!
Sapphire! Franz! Where are you?
The water will soon make
them come out of the Chapel.
- Sapphire!
- Franz!
Sapphire, hold on!
- Franz! Franz!
- Sapphire!
- Franz!
Sapphire! Sapphire!
Sapphire, I will save you!
I will save you at any cost!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP